[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "category": "sweetness",
    "question": "How sweet is ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "Very Sweet", "Sweet", "Dry", "Very Dry"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "category": "body",
    "question": "How would you describe the body of ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "Full Body", "Medium-full Body", "Medium Body", "Medium-light Body", "Light Body"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "category": "tannin",
    "question": "How would you describe the tannin level of ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "High Tannin", "Medium-high Tannin", "Medium Tannin", "Medium-low Tannin", "Low to no Tannin"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "category": "acidity",
    "question": "How would you describe the acidity of ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "High Acidity", "Medium-high Acidity", "Medium Acidity", "Medium-low Acidity", "Low Acidity"]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "category": "alcohol",
    "question": "What is the alcohol by volume of ",
    "falseAnswers": ["10% or less alcohol by volume", "11% Alcohol by volume", "12% Alcohol by volume", "13% Alcohol by volume", "14% Alcohol by volume", "15% or more alcohol by volume"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "category": "temp",
    "question": "At what temperature should you serve ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "38–45°F / 3–7°C", "45–55°F / 7–13°C", "55–60°F / 13–16°C", "Room Temperature"]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "category": "decant",
    "question": "How long should we decant ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "30 minutes", "1 Hour", "2 Hours", "This wine is not decanted"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "category": "ageability",
    "question": "What is the average age for ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "1-3 Years", "3-5 Years", "5-10 Years", "10+ Years"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "category": "region",
    "question": "In what region do they make ",
    "falseAnswers": [ "Bordeaux", "Burgundy", "Champagne", "Loire", "Alsace", "Rhône", "Provence", "Languedoc-Roussillon", "Beaujolais", "Jura", "Piedmont", "Tuscany", "Veneto", "Abruzzo", "Sicily", "Napa", "Oregon", "Sonoma", "Washington State", "Port", "Mendoza", " Patagonia", "Bierzo", "Rioja", "Victoria", "Marlborough"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "category": "country",
    "question": "In what country do they make ",
    "falseAnswers": ["America", "Australia", "Chile", "England", "France", "Germany", "Hungary", "Italy", "New Zealand", "Spain"]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "category": "sparkling",
    "question": "Which accurately describes ",
    "falseAnswers": ["not sparkling", "sparkling"]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "category": "color",
    "question": "What color is ",
    "falseAnswers": ["red", "white", "rosè"]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "category": "primaryFlavors",
    "question": "What is one of the primary flavors of "
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "category": "varietal",
    "question": "What is one of the grape varietals of "
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "category": "pairings",
    "question": "What is one of the food pairings for "
  }
]